

AMOS KIMUTAI KORIR

Software Developer

About me

Highly skilled and motivated Information Technology professional with a proven track record of success in developing, implementing, and managing IT systems.

- 0
- +254 719 388 139
- amoskorir 631@gmail.com
- 0
- Nairobi, Kenya

Language

- English
- Kiswahili (basic)

Expertise

- Management Skills
- Creativity
- Problem Solving
- Analytical
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership

Experience

AKITECH TECHNOLOGIES Nairobi - Kenya 2020 - 2022

Successfully implemented and managed network infrastructure upgrades to enhance system efficiency and decrease downtime.

PANTECH AI New Delhi - India 2016 - 2020

Conducted thorough security audits and implemented comprehensive data protection measures to safeguard against cyber threats.

Studio Showde Nakuru - Kenya 2010 - 2015

Developed custom software solutions to streamline business processes and increase productivity.

Education

Litein High School K.C.S.E

Co-operative University

Bachelor of Information Technology 2014 - 2018

Skills Summary

Software development

78 %

Project Management

81 %